Guide to the Fidelis Zitterbart Manuscripts, 1868-1915 SC.1967.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Air Varie: [no.] 17: [for violin and piano: in A major], July 18, 1883; 1 score (9 p), and violin part (3 p.) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Air Varie: [no.] 17 - Score, July 18, 1883; 1.
  - Air Varie: [no.] 17 - Parts: Violin, July 18, 1883; 2.
- Grand Sonate Pathetique for Violincello and Piano, July 15, 1884; 1 score (20 p.), and violoncello part (6 p.) (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Grand Sonate Pathetique - Score, July 15, 1884; 1.
  - Grand Sonate Pathetique - Parts: Violoncello, July 15, 1884; 2.
- Sonata [no. 1]: [for] Violoncello and Piano: in A Major, July 1, 1871; 1 score (25 p.), and violoncello part (6 p.) (Box 41, Folder 6)
  At head of caption: To Mr. Adolf Hartdegen. 2nd copy has Herrn Hartdegen gewidmet on caption. First copy has the number "8" pasted on caption and part. Location: New York. Piano part is somewhat different between the two scores, but violoncello part remains the same.
  - Sonata [no. 1] - Score, July 1, 1871; 1.
  - Sonata [no. 1] - Parts: Violoncello, July 1, 1871; 2.
- Sonata: No. 3: in A Minor: for Violoncello and Piano, February 1, 1903; 1 score (29 p.), and violoncello part (8 p.) (Box 41, Folder 7)
  The number "558" written in pencil onwrapper. The number "10" pasted on score and part. At head of title: To Mr. Victor Herbert.
  - Sonata: No. 3 - Score, February 1, 1903; 1.
  - Sonata: No. 3 - Parts: Violoncello, February 1, 1903; 2.
- Sonata: [no.] 9: in C Minor: [for] Violoncello and Piano, 1 score (20 p.), and violoncello part (8 p.) (Box 41, Folder 8)
  The number "544" written in pencil on score. On part: (2nd version [in red ink] of 1st mov't.) At head of title: To Mr. Henri Merck. Corrections by the composer in pencil throughout.
  - Sonata: [no.] 9 - Score, 1.
  - Sonata: [no.] 9 - Parts: Violoncello, 2.
- Sonata: [no.] 9: in C Minor: [for] Violoncello et Piano, 1 score (8 p.) (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Meltzer's Sonate: [no.] 12: for Violoncello and Piano: in G Minor, May 15, 1902; 1 score (27 p.), and violoncello part (8 p.) (Box 41, Folder 10)
  The number "546" written on wrapper.
  - Meltzer's Sonate - Score, May 15, 1902; 1.
  - Meltzer's Sonate - Parts: Violoncello, May 15, 1902; 2.
- Var. 5, 1 part (1 p.) (Box 41, Folder 11)
  Incomplete. Not known what other piece this may belong to.
- Caprice Humoresque: in F Major / by Fidelis Zitterbart; full orchestra arrangement by O. E. del Bianco, 1 score (43 p.), flute 1 and 2 part (7 p.), flute 3/piccolo part (3 p.), oboe 1 and 2 part (6 p.), english horn part (3 p.), clarinet 1 and 2 part (8 p.), bass clarinet part (4 p.), bassoon 1 and 2 part (7 p.), bassoon 2 part (4 p.), horn 1 and 2 part (3 p.), horn 3 and 4 part (3 p.), trumpet 1 and 2 part (2 p.), trumpet 3 part (2 p.), trombone 1 and 2 part (3 p.), bass trombone and tuba part (3 p.), timpani part (2 p.), bass drum and cymbal part (2 p.), violin 1 part (9 copies, each 5 p.), violin 2 part (8 copies, each 4 p.), viola part (7 copies, each 4 p.), cello part (6 copies, each 4 p.), bass part (4 parts, each 3 p.), and harp part (6 p.) (Box 41, Folder 12)
  Originally for solo piano; arranged for orchestra. On t.p.: To C.J. Braun. to remember me. 2 copies of score (both facsimiles of the arranger's manuscript; 2nd copy in negative). Some parts in facsimile also.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Score, 1.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Flute 1 and 2, 2.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Flute 3/Piccolo, 3.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Oboe 1 and 2, 4.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: English Horn, 5.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Clarinet 1 and 2, 6.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Bass Clarinet, 7.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Bassoon 1 and 2, 8.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Bassoon 2, 9.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Horn 1 and 2, 10.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Horn 3 and 4, 11.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Trumpet 1 and 2, 12.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Trumpet 3, 13.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Trombone 1 and 2, 14.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Bass Trombone and Tuba, 15.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Timpani, 16.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Bass Drum and Cymbals, 17.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Violin 1, 18.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Violin 2, 19.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Viola, 20.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Violoncello, 21.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Basso, 22.
  - Caprice Humoresque - Parts: Harp, 23.
- Victory March / [by] Fidelis Zitterbart; arr. by E. Beal, piccolo part (1 p.), flute part (1 p.), oboe part (1 p.), bassoon part (1 p.), Eb clarinet part (1 p.), solo Bb clarinet part (2 copies, each 1 page) clarinet 1 part (1 p.), clarinet 2 part (1 p.), clarinet 2 and 3 part (1 p.), conductor part (2 p.), solo cornet part (1 p.), cornet 1 part (1 p.), cornet 2 and 3 part (1 p.), trombone part (1 p.), Eb horn 3 and 4/alto part (1 p.), Eb horn 3 and 4/alto part (1 p.), baritone part (1 p.), treble clef baritone part (2 p.), trombone 1 and 2 part (1 p.), trombone 3 part (1 p.), bass drum/cymbal part (1 p.), snare drum/bells part (1 p.), solo bass part (1 p.), and basses part (1 p.) (Box 42, Folder 1)
  Originally for piano. On wrapper: Arranged for military band.Two sets of parts; one in manuscript; the other in photocopy. Some parts have additional measures pasted in.
  - Victory March - Parts: Piccolo, 1.
  - Victory March - Parts: Flute, 2.
  - Victory March - Parts: Oboe, 3.
  - Victory March - Parts: Bassoon, 4.
  - Victory March - Parts: Eb Clarinet, 5.
  - Victory March - Parts: Solo Bb Clarinet, 6.
  - Victory March - Parts: Bb Clarinet 1, 7.
  - Victory March - Parts: Bb Clarinet 2, 8.
  - Victory March - Parts: Bb Clarinet 2 and 3, 9.
  - Victory March - Parts: Conductor, 10.
  - Victory March - Parts: Solo Cornet, 11.
  - Victory March - Parts: Cornet 1, 12.
  - Victory March - Parts: Cornet 2 and 3, 13.
  - Victory March - Parts: Trombone 1, 14.
  - Victory March - Parts: Eb Horn 1 and 2/Alto, 15.
  - Victory March - Parts: Eb Horn 3 and 4/Alto, 16.
  - Victory March - Parts: Baritone, 17.
  - Victory March - Parts: Treble Clef Baritone, 18.
  - Victory March - Parts: Trombone 1 and 2, 19.
  - Victory March - Parts: Trombone 3, 20.
  - Victory March - Parts: Bass Drum/Cymbal, 21.
  - Victory March - Parts: Snare Drum/Bells, 22.
  - Victory March - Parts: Solo Bass, 23.
  - Victory March - Parts: Basses, 24.
- March in Eb Major, Liberty / by Fidelis Zitterbart; arranged by Jean de Backer and Paul Henneberg, 1 score (11 p.), piccolo part (1 p.), flute part (1 p.), oboe part (2 copies, each 1 p.), oboe 2 part (1 p.), bassoon 1 part (1 p.), bassoon 2 part (1 part), Eb clarinet part (1 p.), Bb clarinet part (2 copies, each 1 p.), Bb clarinet 2 part (1 p.), Bb clarinet 3 part ( 2 copies, each 1 p.), soprano saxaphone part (1 p.), alto saxaphone part (1 p.), solo cornet part (1 p.), cornet 1 part (1 p.), cornet 2 part (1 p.), flugelhorn 1 part (1 p.), flugelhorn 2 part (1 p.) trumpet 1 part (1 p.), trumpet 2 part (1 p.), horn 1 part (1 p.), horn 2 part (1 p.), horn 3 part (1 p.), horn 4 part (1 p.), euphonium part (1 p.), baritone part (1 p.), trombone 1 part (1 p.), trombone 2 part (1 p.), bass trombone part (1 p.), tuba 1 part (1 p.), tuba 2 part (1 p.), drum part (1 p.), and grand cassa part (1 p.) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  Originally for piano; arranged for concert band. Version in E-flat major.
  - March in Eb Major - Score, 1.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Piccolo, 2.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Flute, 3.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Oboe, 4.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Bassoon 1, 5.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Bassoon 2, 6.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Eb Clarinet, 7.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Bb Clarinet 1, 8.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Bb Clarinet 2, 9.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Bb Clarinet 3, 10.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Soprano Saxophone, 11.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Alto Saxophone, 12.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Solo Cornet, 13.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Cornet 1, 14.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Cornet 2, 15.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Flugelhorn 1, 16.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Flugelhorn 2, 17.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Trumpet 1, 18.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Trumpet 2, 19.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Horn 1, 20.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Horn 2, 21.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Horn 3, 22.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Horn 4, 23.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Euphonium, 24.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Baritone, 25.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Trombone 1, 26.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Trombone 2, 27.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Bass Trombone, 28.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Tuba 1, 29.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Tuba 2, 30.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Drum, 31.
  - March in Eb Major - Parts: Grand Cassa, 32.
- March: Liberty, 1 score (6 p.), piccolo part (1 p.), Eb clarinet part (1 p.), clarinet 1 part (1 p.), clarinet 2 part (2 copies, each 1 p.), clarinet 2 and 3 part (1 p.), oboe part (1 p.), bassoon part (1 p.), alto saxaphone (1 p.), tenor saxaphone part (1 p.), baritone saxaphone part (1 p.), Eb cornet part (1 p.)m solo Bb cornet part (1 p.), Bb cornet 1 part (1 p.), Bb cornet 2 and three part (1 p.), horn 1 and 2 part (1 p.), horn 3 and 4 part (1 p.), trombones 1 and 2 part (1 p.), trombone 3 part (1 p.), baritone part (1 p.), tuba part (1 p.), and drums part (1 p.) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  Originally for piano; arranged for concetr band. Version in D major. Score in oblong format. All parts are stamped with: "Everything in Music" / W. Paris Chambers / 34 East 14th Street, / New York. Written in pencil at bottom of piccolo part" Put this in for Sunday / 1st number.
  - March: Liberty - Score, 1.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Piccolo, 2.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Eb Clarinet, 3.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Bb Clarinet 1, 4.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Bb Clarinet 2 and 3, 5.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Oboe, 6.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Bassoon, 7.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Alto Saxaphone, 8.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Tenor Saxaphone, 9.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Baritone Saxaphone, 10.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Eb Cornet, 11.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Solo Bb Cornet, 12.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Bb Cornet 1, 13.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Bb Cornet 2 and 3, 14.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Horns 1 and 2, 15.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Horns 3 and 4, 16.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Trombones 1 and 2, 17.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Trombone 3, 18.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Baritone, 19.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Tuba, 20.
  - March: Liberty - Parts: Drums, 21.
- March: Liberty, 3 versions, (each 3 p.) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  Three versions of the same piece. First and second versions differ in note values and some melodic variation. The number "4" written in pencil on caption of 1st version. The 3rd version (possibly the original?) has numerous corrections and additions in pencil. Title in ink on this version given as: McKinely and Hobart: Inaugural March which is crossed out in pencil and March (Liberty) written in.
- March: Victory: [for] Piano, 3 p. of music (Box 42, Folder 5)
  The number "1020" written in ink on score. In A major, but different than the orchestral march of the same title, and the brass arrangement.
- March: for Piano: [in A minor], 3 p. of music (Box 42, Folder 6)
  The number "2" written in pencil on caption.
- Fantasie Dramatique: for Piano, October 20, 1883; 11 p. of music (Box 42, Folder 7)
  On cover: Elegy written in a country church yard by Thomas Grey. Text of poem pasted on inside cover and wriiten throughout music. Caption title: Dramatische Fantasie (für Piano).
- Romeo and Juliet: Adagio con Moto quasi Andante: für Orchester: "Balcony Scene", March 8, 1874; 1 score (9 p.), also 1 handwritten score flute part (1 p.), oboe part (1 p.), clarinet 1 part (1 p.), clarinet 2 part (1 p.), bassoon 1 part (1 p.), bassoon 2 part (1 p.), horn 1 part (1 p.), horn 2 part (1 p.), timpani part (1 p.), violin 1 part (3 copies, each 1 p.), violin 2 part (2 copies, each 1 p.), viola part (2 copies, each 1 p.), violoncello part (2 copies, each 1 p.), and bass part (2 copies, each 1 p.) violin (Box 42, Folder 8)
  Very brittle. 2 copies of score. Copy 1 is the final copy in black ink. Oblong format. On cover in pencil: unfinished. At head of title: Meinem Freund William Spriestersbach gewidmet. At end of score is the manuscript in pencil for Air varia for violin and piano ([3] p.). Copy 2 is the fair copy in pencil with original title: Midnight (scratched out and Balcony scene written in). Subtitle given as "Dramatic Music". Following score is the sketches for the 2nd movement, titled "Morning," which is crossed out in black ink. Manuscript parts have title: Midnight, Garden scene.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Score, March 8, 1874; 1.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Flute, March 8, 1874; 2.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Oboe, March 8, 1874; 3.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Clarinet 1, March 8, 1874; 4.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Clarinet 2, March 8, 1874; 5.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Bassoon 1, March 8, 1874; 6.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Bassoon 2, March 8, 1874; 7.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Horn 1, March 8, 1874; 8.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Horn 2, March 8, 1874; 9.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Timpani, March 8, 1874; 10.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Violin 1, March 8, 1874; 11.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Violin 2, March 8, 1874; 12.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Viola, March 8, 1874; 13.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Violoncello, March 8, 1874; 14.
  - Romeo and Juliet - Parts: Bass, March 8, 1874; 15.
- Undine Overture for Orchestra, October 17, 1890; 1 score (17 p.), flute 1 and 2 part (2 p.), oboe part (2 p.), clarinet part (2 p.), bassoon part (2 p.), trumpet part (2 p.), horn 1 and 2 part (2 p.), trombone part (2 p.), piano part (3 p.), violin principal part (3 p.), violin 1 part (2 parts, each 3 p.), violin 2 part (3 parts, each 3 p.), part for 2 violas (3 p.), violoncello part (3 p.), and bass part (2 p.) (Box 43, Folder 1)
  In pencil. Parts in black ink. Score in oblong format; parts in upright format. Subtitles on caption: Ouverture in C moll; Knight Hildebrand and his steed. Brittle.
  - Undine Overture - Score, October 17, 1890; 1.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Flutes 1 and 2, October 17, 1890; 2.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Oboe, October 17, 1890; 3.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Clarinet, October 17, 1890; 4.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Bassoon, October 17, 1890; 5.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Trumpet, October 17, 1890; 6.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Horn 1 and 2, October 17, 1890; 7.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Trombone, October 17, 1890; 8.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Piano, October 17, 1890; 9.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Principal Violin, October 17, 1890; 10.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Violin 1, October 17, 1890; 11.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Violin 2, October 17, 1890; 12.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: 2 Violas, October 17, 1890; 13.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Violoncello, October 17, 1890; 14.
  - Undine Overture - Parts: Bass, October 17, 1890; 15.
- Yuletide, or at 3. a.m.: Ouverture for Orchestra, December 21, 1910; 1 score (31 p.), flute part (3 p.), oboe part (3 p.), clarinet 1 part (3 p.), clarinet 2 part (3 p.), bassoon part (3 p.), cornet 1 part (3 p.), cornet 2 part (3 p.), horn 1 part (2 p.), horn 2 part (2 p.), trombone part (3 p.), drum et grand-cassa part (2 p.), violin principal part (3 p.), violin 1 part (2 copies, each 3 p.), violin 2 part (2 copies, each 3 p.), viola part (3 p.), violoncello part (3 p.), bass part (3 p.), and piano part (7 p.) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  Decorative border on t.p.
  - Yuletide - Score, December 21, 1910; 1.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Flute, December 21, 1910; 2.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Oboe, December 21, 1910; 3.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Clarinet 1, December 21, 1910; 4.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Clarinet 2, December 21, 1910; 5.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Bassoon, December 21, 1910; 6.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Cornet 1, December 21, 1910; 7.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Cornet 2, December 21, 1910; 8.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Horn 1, December 21, 1910; 9.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Horn 2, December 21, 1910; 10.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Trombone, December 21, 1910; 11.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Drum et Grand-Cassa, December 21, 1910; 12.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Violin Principal, December 21, 1910; 13.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Violin 1, December 21, 1910; 14.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Violin 2, December 21, 1910; 15.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Viola, December 21, 1910; 16.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Violoncello, December 21, 1910; 17.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Bass, December 21, 1910; 18.
  - Yuletide - Parts: Piano, December 21, 1910; 19.
- Fidelis: or The Dream: Ouverture for Grand Orchestra, September 30, 1886; 1 score (23 p.), flute part (3 p.), flute 2 and 3 part (3 p.), oboe 1 and 2 part (3 p.), clarinet 1 part (3 p.), clarinet 2 part (3 p.), bassoon 1 part (3 p.), bassoon 2 part (3 p.), trumpet 1 part (2 p.), trumpet 2 part (2 p.), horn 1 part (2 p.), horn 2 part (2 p.), trombone part (2 p.), timpani part (2 p.), violin principal part (4 p.), violin 1 part (4 copies, one is a different version, each 3 p.), violin 2 part (3 copies, each 3 p.), viola part (2 copies, each 3 p.), violoncello part (2 copies, each 3 p.), and bass part (2 copies, each 3 p.) (Box 43, Folder 3)
  Title on wrapper: Der Fidelis, oder Die Traum-Oüvertüre. Work was begun on 09/02/1885 and completed on 09/30/1886.
  - Fidelis - Score, September 30, 1886; 1.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Flute 1, September 30, 1886; 2.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Flute 2 and 3, September 30, 1886; 3.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Oboe 1 and 2, September 30, 1886; 4.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Clarinet 1, September 30, 1886; 5.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Clarinet 2, September 30, 1886; 6.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Bassoon 1, September 30, 1886; 7.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Bassoon 2, September 30, 1886; 8.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Trumpet 1, September 30, 1886; 9.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Trumpet 2, September 30, 1886; 10.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Horn 1, September 30, 1886; 11.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Horn 2, September 30, 1886; 12.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Trombone, September 30, 1886; 13.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Timpani, September 30, 1886; 14.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Violin Principal, September 30, 1886; 15.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Violin 1, September 30, 1886; 16.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Violin 2, September 30, 1886; 17.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Viola, September 30, 1886; 18.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Violoncello, September 30, 1886; 19.
  - Fidelis - Parts: Bass, September 30, 1886; 20.
- Fidelis: oder Die Traum: Ouverture: for Violin and Piano, September 15, 1885; 1 score (8 p.) (Box 43, Folder 4)
  Date on cover given as 09/02/1885. Date of completion at end. Original version of orchestral work? It is possible to play this work using the Violin I part from the orchestrated version.
- Puss in Boots: Ouverture for Orchestra, November 19, 1889; 1 score (25 p.), flute 1 part (3 p.), flute 2 part (3 p.), oboe 1 part (3 p.), oboe 2 part (2 p.), clarinet 1 part (3 p.), clarinet 2 part (3 p.), bassoon 1 part (3 p.), bassoon 2 part (3 p.), trumpet 1 part (2 p.), trumpet 2 part (2 p.), horn 1 part (3 p.), horn 2 part (3 p.), horn 3 part (3 p.), trombone part (3 p.), timpani part (2 p.), violin principal part (4 p.), violin 1 part (2 copies, each 4 p.), violin 2 part (3 copies, each 4 p.), viola part (4 p.), violoncello part (4 p.), and bass part (3 p.) (Box 43, Folder 5)
  Score in pencil and in oblong format; parts in upright format. At top of part for Flute I: T. B. Atterbury Jr.
  - Puss in Boots - Score, November 19, 1889; 1.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Flute 1, November 19, 1889; 2.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Flute 2, November 19, 1889; 3.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Oboe 1, November 19, 1889; 4.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Oboe 2, November 19, 1889; 5.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Clarinet 1, November 19, 1889; 6.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Clarinet 2, November 19, 1889; 7.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Bassoon 1, November 19, 1889; 8.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Bassoon 2, November 19, 1889; 9.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Trumpet 1, November 19, 1889; 10.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Trumpet 2, November 19, 1889; 11.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Horn 1, November 19, 1889; 12.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Horn 2, November 19, 1889; 13.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Horn 3, November 19, 1889; 14.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Trombone, November 19, 1889; 15.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Timpani, November 19, 1889; 16.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Violin Principal, November 19, 1889; 17.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Violin 1, November 19, 1889; 18.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Violin 2, November 19, 1889; 19.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Viola, November 19, 1889; 20.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Violoncello, November 19, 1889; 21.
  - Puss in Boots - Parts: Bass, November 19, 1889; 22.
- Fantasy: in D Major: for Violin, Viola, and Piano, September 10, 1912; 2 scores (8, and 10 p.), violin part (2 p.), and viola part (2 p.) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  2 copies of score. Copy 1 is the final copy in black ink. Copy 2 (10 p.) is the fair copy in pencil.
  - Fantasy: in D Major - Score 1, September 10, 1912; 1.
  - Fantasy: in D Major - Score 2, September 10, 1912; 2.
  - Fantasy: in D Major - Parts: Violin, September 10, 1912; 3.
  - Fantasy: in D Major - Parts: Viola, September 10, 1912; 4.
- American Suite: in D Minor: [for violin, viola] and Piano, 1 score (22 p.), violin part (7 p.), and viola part (7 p.) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  The number "11" pasted on caption and parts. Contents: Praeludio: Arrival of the guests -- The language of the flowers -- Sherzo: Dangerous pleasures -- The meditation and promenade in the garden -- Ceremonious dedication.
  - American Suite - Score, 1.
  - American Suite - Parts: Violin, 2.
  - American Suite - Parts: Viola, 3.
- Cleopatra: Last Act: Asp Scene: for Orchestra, April 27, 1892; 1 score (13 p.), flute part (1 p.), oboe part (1 p.), clarinet 1 and 2 part (2 p.), bassoon 1 and 2 part (1 p.), cornet part (1 p.), horn part (1 p.), trombone part (1 p.), timpani part (1 p.), violin principal part (2 p.), violin 1 part (2 copies, each 2 p.), violin 2 part (3 copies, each 2 p.), viola part (2 p.), violoncello 1 part (2 p.), violoncello 2 part (2 p.), and bass part (2 p.) (Box 44, Folder 2)
  Score in pencil; parts in black ink.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Score, April 27, 1892; 1.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Flute, April 27, 1892; 2.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Oboe, April 27, 1892; 3.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Clarinet 1 and 2, April 27, 1892; 4.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Bassoon 1 and 2, April 27, 1892; 5.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Cornet, April 27, 1892; 6.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Horn, April 27, 1892; 7.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Trombone, April 27, 1892; 8.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Timpani, April 27, 1892; 9.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Violin Principal, April 27, 1892; 10.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Violin 1, April 27, 1892; 11.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Violin 2, April 27, 1892; 12.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Viola, April 27, 1892; 13.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Violoncello 1, April 27, 1892; 14.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Violoncello 2, April 27, 1892; 15.
  - Cleopatra: Last Act - Parts: Bass, April 27, 1892; 16.
- The Queen's Worship: Meditation: for Orchestra, flute part (1 p.), oboe part (1 p.), clarinet 1 part (1 p.), clarinet 2 part (1 p.), bassoon part (1 p.), cornet 1 part (1 p.), cornet 2 part (1 p.), horn 1 and 2 part (1 p.), trombone part (1 p.), drum part (1 p.), violin 1 part (2 copies, each 1 p.), violin 2 part (2 copies, each 1 p.), viola part (1 p.), violoncello part (1 p.), bass part (1 p.), and piano part (2 p.) (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - The Queen's Worship - Parts: Flute, 1.